Berking, Max; Papers apap228
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Max Berking Papers
1964-1965
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Berking, Max, 1917-1997
apap228
3.4 cubic ft.
The Max Berking Papers, 1964-1965 collection contains materials related to Max Berking's service in the New York State Senate from 1964 to 1965.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
Max Berking initially donated his papers to Syracuse University in 1971. In 2006, the papers were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Biographical Sketch
Max Berking was a Democratic Party activist who served in the New York State Senate during the years 1964-1965.
Born in 1917, Berking was raised in Greenwich, Connecticut, where his grandfather was a Republican State Senator. He attended Brunswick School in Greenwich and Williams College in western Massachusetts, where he was exposed to liberal politics by the professor and columnist Max Lerner. During World War II he served on the Fair Employment Practice Committee, which worked to fight discrimination in war industries.
After the war Berking established an ad agency in Manhattan and settled in the Westchester County city of Rye, where he served as Rye Democratic Party Chairman. In 1964, Berking ran to fill the remaining year of a four-year term as New York State Senator from the 30th District, which at that time encompassed southeastern Westchester County. He served until 1965 and was not reelected.
Following his departure from the Senate Berking remained active in local politics. From 1971 to 1975 he served as chairman of the Westchester County Democratic Party. In 1982 he retired to Northport, Florida, where he died in 1997.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials related to Max Berking's service in the New York State Senate from 1964 to 1965.
Series 1, Subject File, contains files on various subjects. These files typically contain research material and correspondence with constituents. Subjects include the proposed statewide sales tax, government intervention to save the New Haven Railroad, the debate over pornography sales on newsstands, and the establishment of Westchester Community College. This series is organized alphabetically by subject.
Series 2, Senate Bills, contains material on various New York State Senate bills with which Berking was involved. Some of these files contain notes and drafts related to the bill in question, while others just contain a print copy of the proposed bill. These files are arranged according to the serial numbers assigned to each bill by the legislature.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1: Subject File, 2.2 cubic ft.
Series 2: Senate Bills, 1.2 cubic ft.
Series 1 is organized alphabetically by subject. Series 2 is arranged according to the serial numbers assigned to each bill by the legislature.
Politics and Politicians; New York (State). Legislature. Senate; New York State; Letters; Bills, Legislative; Berking, Max, 1917-; Senate of New-York
- Subject File, 1964-1965; 1; 2.2 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  This series is organized alphabetically by subject.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains files on various subjects. These files typically contain research material and correspondence with constituents. Subjects include the proposed statewide sales tax, government intervention to save the New Haven Railroad, the debate over pornography sales on newsstands, and the establishment of Westchester Community College.
  - A - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 1)
  - Aged, Problems of, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 2)
  - Alcohol, Alcoholism, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 3)
  - Alcohol - Drinking Age, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 4)
  - Alcohol - Licenses, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 5)
  - Alcohol - Raise Drinking Age Letters Answered with Sample, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 6)
  - Animal/Bird Legislation, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 7)
  - B - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 8)
  - Berking - Biographical, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Berking - Favors Asked, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Berking - "Mash Notes", 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 11)
  - Berking - Meetings, Invitations, Etc., 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Berking - Personal, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 13)
  - Bills Offered Us, but Rejected, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Boxing, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Budget - Proposed State, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 16)
  - C - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Capital Punishment, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 18)
  - Children, Interests of, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Cigarette Labelling & Smoking, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Citizens' Union, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 21)
  - D - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 22)
  - Divorce Laws, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 23)
  - E - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 24)
  - East Hudson Parkway, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 25)
  - Education - Routine Letters on Bronston Bill, 1069-E, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 26)
  - Education Law - Bronston Bill SIL069, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 27)
  - Education Law - Tax Reserve Bill, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 28)
  - F - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 29)
  - Firearms, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 30)
  - Firemen & Policemen, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 31)
  - Full Crew Law, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 32)
  - G - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 33)
  - Gambling - Lotteries, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 34)
  - H - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 35)
  - Highway Legislation, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 36)
  - Hospitals, State, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 37)
  - Housing, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 38)
  - Human Rights Legislation, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 39)
  - I - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 40)
  - Insurance, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 41)
  - J - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 42)
  - Job Development Authority, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 43)
  - Judiciary, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 44)
  - K - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 45)
  - L - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 46)
  - League of Women Voters, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 47)
  - Legislative Reform, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 48)
  - Letter to Editor Re: Hospital Unionization Bill, Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 49)
  - Local Government Seminar, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 50)
  - Long Island Bridge, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 51)
  - M - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 52)
  - Memoranda on Bills, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 53)
  - Memorandum in Support of Senate Int. No. 4204, Print 4712, by Senators Berking, Berman, Letsen, and Ohrenstein, Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 54)
  - Minimum Wage, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous Letters - Various Issues - Letter "G" of Agreement Sent, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous Letters - Various Issues - Letter "K" Hedge Sent, Undated (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 57)
  - N - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 58)
  - Narcotics, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Subject File), Folder 59)
  - New Haven Railroad, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 1)
  - New Haven Railroad - Article Reprint, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 2)
  - New Haven Railroad - Helpers, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 3)
  - New Haven Railroad - Municipal Resolutions, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 4)
  - New Haven Railroad - Original Bill Drafts, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 5)
  - New Haven Railroad - Releases, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 6)
  - New Haven Railroad - Routine, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 7)
  - New Haven Railroad - Routine Letters Answered - Sample "D", Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 8)
  - New Rochelle Parking Authority, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 9)
  - News Clipping - Local Action on "Teenage Drinks", Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, 1964-1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 11)
  - Noise Abatement, Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Norman - Actions to be Taken, 1964-1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 13)
  - O - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Off-Track Betting, Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 15)
  - Opticians, Optometrists Etc., 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 16)
  - P - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 17)
  - Penal Law, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 18)
  - Playland, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 19)
  - Pornography, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 20)
  - Pornography Letters Answered Routinely and by Pool Sample H, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 21)
  - Poverty, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 22)
  - Press Release: "Berking Hits Sales Tax as Bad for County", Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 23)
  - Prisons (Crime, etc.), 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 24)
  - Public Health, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 25)
  - Public Works, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 26)
  - Pure Waters Program, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 27)
  - Q - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 28)
  - R - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 29)
  - Reapportionment, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 30)
  - Retailers, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 31)
  - Rye - City & Town, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 32)
  - S - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 33)
  - School Assessment Bill, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 34)
  - Schools - Education Law, Undated (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 35)
  - Schools - Out of State Scholarships, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 36)
  - Schools - Requests for College Admissions, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 37)
  - Schools - Shared Time, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 38)
  - Schools - SUNY - Westchester, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 39)
  - Schools - Teachers (Current), 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 40)
  - Schools - Teachers (Retired), 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 41)
  - Schools - Westchester Community College, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 42)
  - State Conservation Department Annual Report, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 43)
  - State Investigation Commission, 1965 (Box 2 (1-Subject File), Folder 44)
  - Storm King Mountain Project, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 1)
  - Strikebreaker Bill, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 2)
  - Surplus Food, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 3)
  - Taxes - Auto and Gas Taxes - Answered by Sample C, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 4)
  - Taxes - Proposed Cigarette Tax, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 5)
  - Taxes - Proposed Sales Tax, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 6)
  - Taxes - Sales Tax Letters Answered by #1 Sample Letter, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 7)
  - Taxes - Sales Tax Letters Answered by #2 Sample Letter, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 8)
  - Taxes - Sales Tax Mailing, 8/1/65, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 9)
  - Textbooks (Fair, Shared-Time, Minority), 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 10)
  - Town Manager Bill, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 11)
  - "Truth in Leading" Legislation, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 12)
  - Venereal Disease, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 13)
  - W - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 14)
  - Welfare, Social, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 15)
  - XYZ - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 3 (1-Subject File), Folder 16)
- Senate Bills, 1965; 2; 1.2 cubic ft.
  These files are arranged according to the serial numbers assigned to each bill by the legislature.
  This series contains material on various New York State Senate bills with which Berking was involved. Some of these files contain notes and drafts related to the bill in question, while others just contain a print copy of the proposed bill. These files are arranged according to the serial numbers assigned to each bill by the legislature.
  - Print. 112, 2049 / Intro. 112 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Regents College Scholarships and Fellowships, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 17)
  - Print. 465 / Intro. 465 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Permitting Attendance by Regents Scholarship Recipients at Approved Colleges and Universities within the United States, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 18)
  - Print. S. 565, 4194, A. 1238, 6103 / Intro S. 565, A. 1238 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Making it Optional for Certain School Districts to Maintain a Reserve for Uncollected Taxes, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 19)
  - Print. 575 / Intro. 575 - To Amend the Mental Hygiene Law, in Relation to Construction Costs Subject to State Reimbursement for Community Mental Health Services, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 20)
  - Print. 576 / Intro. 576 - To Amend the Mental Hygiene Law, in Relation to Expenditures Subject to State Reimbursement for Community Mental Health Services, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 21)
  - Print S. 583, A. 1321 / Intro. S. 583, A. 1321 - To Amend the Navigation Law and the Code of Criminal Procedure, in Relation to Enforcement of Navigation Laws by Cities, Towns, and Villages, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 22)
  - Print. 646 / Intro. 646 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Power of Boards of Education to Ban Fraternities and Sororities in High Schools, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 23)
  - Print. 647 / Intro. 647 - To Amend the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, in Relation to Local Option for Sale of Alcoholic Beverages for On-Premise Consumption Between Certain Hours, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 24)
  - Print. 772 / Intro. 772 - To Authorize and Empower the City of Rye to Convey to the Rye Free Reading Room a Portion of Certain Lands Acquired by the City of Rye for Park Purposes, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 25)
  - Print. 773 / Intro. 773 - To Amend the Legislative Law, in Relation to Providing an Electrical Roll Call Apparatus to Record the Votes of Members of the Legislature, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 26)
  - Print. 774 / Intro. 774 - To Amend the Legislative Law, in Relation to Establishing the Hours of the Day when the Senate and/or Assembly Shall Not Be in Session, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 27)
  - Print. 775 / Intro. 775 - To Amend the Legislative Law, in Relation to the Right of the Ranking Minority Members of the Finance Committee of the Senate and the Ways and Means Committee of the Assembly to Attend Hearings and Make Inquiries on Estimates for and Revision of the Budget, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 28)
  - Print. 776 / Intro. 776 - To Amend the Legislative Law, in Relation to the Authorizing the Consideration of Bills by the Legislature Without Reintroduction Thereof During the Second Year of the Term of Such Legislature, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 29)
  - Print. 777 / Intro. 777 - To Amend the Legislative Law, in Relation to the Publication of Verbatim Transcripts of the Proceedings of the Legislature, and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 30)
  - Print. 778 / Intro. 778 - To Amend the Labor Law, in Relation to Authorizing the Establishment of a Youth Training Corps to Provide Training and Employment for Young Men in the Various State Departments and Agencies, Authorizing Local Area Youth Employment Programs, and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 31)
  - Print. 779 / Intro. 779 - To Amend the Public Authorities Law, in Relation to the Establishment of the Commuter Railroad Authority, Defining its Powers and Duties, Providing for Advances and Other Assistance Thereto, and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 32)
  - Print. 1075 / Intro. 1076 - To Amend the Railroad Law, in Relation to the Establishment of the New York Transportation Agency, Defining its Powers and Duties, and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 33)
  - Print. 1076, 2250 / Intro. 1076 - To Amend the Labor Law, in Relation to Definition of "Non-Profitmaking or Residential Care Center", 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 34)
  - Print. 1414 / Intro. 1400 - To Amend the Labor Law, in Relation to Increasing the Statutory Minimum Wage to One Dollar Fifty Cents an Hour, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 35)
  - Print. 2276 / Intro. 2209 - To Amend the Social Welfare Law, in Relation to Powers and Duties of the Commissioner and Board of Social Welfare, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 36)
  - Print. 2474 / Intro. 2387 - To Amend Chapter One Hundred Four of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Thirty-Six, Entitled "An Act Providing for the Establishment, Organization, and Operation of Police Departments in the Towns of Westchester County," in Relation to Privileges and Immunities of Town Policemen in Such County, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 37)
  - Print. 2475 / Intro. 2388 - To Amend the Village Law, in Relation to Certain Acts of Village Policemen in Westchester County, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 38)
  - Print. 2689 / Intro. 2570 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to Powers of Boards of Education to Abolish and Ban Fraternities, Sororities and Secret Societies in Secondary Schools, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 39)
  - Print. 2690 / Intro. 2571 - To Amend the Legislative Law, in Relation to Code of Ethics, Undated (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 40)
  - Print. 2691 / Intro. 2572 - Creating a Temporary State Commission to Make a Comprehensive Study of Existing State and Local Laws, Regulations and Codes Relating to Standards for Existing Housing Throughout the State to Determine the Adequacy and Effectiveness Thereof for the Protection and Advancement of the Public Health, Safety and General Welfare and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 41)
  - Print. 2692 / Intro. 2573 - To Authorize and Empower the Town of Mamaroneck to Convey a Parcel of Park Land to the Board of Education, Union Free School District No. 1, Town of Mamaroneck, Westchester County, New York, for Educational Purposes, Undated (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 42)
  - Print S.2886, A. 4880 / Intro. S.2745, A. 4757 - To Amend the Public Authorities Law, in Relation to Providing Penalties for Violations of the Law and Regulations Respecting the Erection and Maintenance of Advertising Devices, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 43)
  - Print. S. 2887, A. 4881 / Intro. S. 2746, A. 4758 - To Amend the Public Authorities Law, in Relation to Granting Rights to the Use and Occupancy of Real Property of the New York State Thruway Authority, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 44)
  - Print. 2908, 4909 / Intro. 2752 - To Amend the Social Welfare Law, in Relation to Day Care for Certain Children and Providing State Reimbursement Therefor in Certain Cases and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 45)
  - Print. 2909, 4185 / Intro. 2753 - To Amend the Social Welfare Law, in Relation to Eligibility for Medical Assistance for the Aged, Services Included in Such Assistance, Legal Responsibility of Relatives in Connection with Such Assistance, and Burial Reserves for Certain Applicants for or Recipients of Such Assistance, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 46)
  - Print. 3063, 3139 / Intro. 2907 - To Amend the Labor Law, in Relation to Increasing the Statutory Minimum Wage to One Dollar and Fifty Cents Per Hour, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 47)
  - Print. 3127 / Intro. 2970 - To Amend the State Finance Law, in Relation to Commencing the Fiscal Year of the State on July First, Nineteen Hundred Sixty-Five, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 48)
  - Print. 3192 / Intro. 2015 - To Amend the Public Authorities Law, in Relation to the Creation of the City of New Rochelle Parking Authority, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 49)
  - Print. 3193 / Intro. 3016 - To Amend Chapter Four Hundred Thirty of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Thirty Eight, Entitled "An Act to Authorize and Enable the Village of Larchmont and the Town Board of the Town of Mamaroneck, Acting for Refuse and Garbage District Number one of the Town of Mamaroneck, County of Westchester, Jointly to Construct and Maintain an Incineration Disposal Plant for Refuse and Garbage in the Town of Mamaroneck, Westchester County, and to Severally Issue Bonds or Other Obligations to Defray the Cost Thereof, and to Validate the Establishment of Refuse and Garbage District Number One of the Town of Mamaroneck," in Relation to Appointments of Members of the Joint Board of Control of the Incinerator Plant Jointly Operated by the Village of Larchmont and the Town of Mamaroneck, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 50)
  - Print. 3310 / Intro. 3124 - To Amend Chapter Nine Hundred Eighty-Nine of the Laws of Nineteen Hundred Fifty-Eight, Entitled "An Act Creating a Temporary State Commission of Investigation; Prescribing its Functions, Powers, and Duties; Marking an Appropriation Therefor, Abolishing the Office of Commissioner of Investigation and Repealing the Provisions of the Executive Law with Respect Thereto; and Amending the Code of Criminal Procedure, in Relation to the Designation of investigators of Such Commission as Peace Officers," in Relation to Extending the Provisions of Such Chapter and the Existence of Such Commission Until April Thirtieth, Nineteen Hundred Seventy, and to the Qualifications of the Members of Such Commission, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 51)
  - Print. 3311, 4230 / Intro. 3155 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Number of Years Required for a Course in a School of Podiatry Leading to a Doctor's Degree in Podiatry, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 52)
  - Print. 3362 / Intro. 3155 - To Amend the Election Law, in Relation to the Future Statewide Application of Permanent Personal Registration, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 53)
  - Print. S. 3464, A. 5311 / Intro. S.3240, A.5085 - To Amend the Education Law, in Relation to the Powers and Duties of Boards of Cooperative Educational Services, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 54)
  - Print. 3475 / Intro. 3251 - To Amend the Workmen's Compensation Law, in Relation to Increasing Compensation Benefits in Disability and Death Cases, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 55)
  - Print. 3479 / Intro. 3255 - To Amend the Penal Law, in Relation to Offense for One under Twenty-One Years of Age to Purchase of Attempt to Purchase Alcoholic Beverages through Fraudulent Means, in Certain Cities or Towns, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 56)
  - Print. 3480 / Intro. 3256 - To Amend the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, in Relation to Local Option for Sale of Alcoholic Beverages to Persons Under Twenty-One Years of Age, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 57)
  - Print. 3501 / Intro. 3277 - To Amend the State Finance Law, in Relation to the Certification or Approval of Accounts and Vouchers of State Departments and Agencies, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Senate Bills), Folder 58)